[
  {
    "front": "acheter",
    "back": "買"
  },
  {
    "front": "vendre",
    "back": "売"
  },
  {
    "front": "pas, marcher",
    "back": "歩"
  },
  {
    "front": "article, produits",
    "back": "品"
  },
  {
    "front": "objet, chose",
    "back": "物"
  },
  {
    "front": "force, puissance, pouvoir",
    "back": "力"
  },
  {
    "front": "son, bruit",
    "back": "音"
  },
  {
    "front": "musique, amusant, facile",
    "back": "楽"
  },
  {
    "front": "large, grand, vaste",
    "back": "広"
  },
  {
    "front": "goût, saveur",
    "back": "味"
  }
]
